Start by switching to the right gear.
This one would fit and use for it
Protection you have for saw blade and grassy.
But I put on the protection that is to the trimmer wire because I suspect that
It will go about some stuff with this.
The next step is to rake the paving to the habitual
and get away as much stone as possible, so I suspect it
Will splash down this aggregate and then Happi may go in.
This is no activity you do
Together with the dog, but she has to wait while I give up on this.
This is the first time I try with
This one, so hopefully it goes as it is intended.
Here we go!
Yes, it was definitely a dirty job.
You might have done it before there was so much soil on top.
But now I have gone over so I have to take and rake away and sweep and see the result.
I guess it may require another round, but decent promised.
I had problems.
I didn't really know.
Because when it has gone this far for this paving
You do not know how large the paving is, but think that the edges only had soil.
But then you start shoveling a little neighbor, or